Neveh Allon

Web Developer

Focused Full-stack Development student currently attending HackerU. Aiming to leverage proven problem-solving, research, and language skills to successfully fill the Web Developer role at your company. Frequently praised as hard-working by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.



NevehAllon@gmail.com



0525355320



Jerusalem, Israel



nevehallon.github.io/portfoli o 2021

in

linkedin.com/in/neveh-allon



github.com/nevehallon



stackoverflow.com/users/935 6733/neveh

SKILLS

Angular

TypeScript

React.js

Node.is

Material

Bootstrap

JQuery

SASS

SQL

NoSQL

Docker

Git

Google Cloud

Wordpress

PHP

LANGUAGES

English

Native / Bilingual Proficiency

Hebrew

Native / Bilingual Proficiency

EDUCATION

Full-stack Web Development

HackerU

10/2019 - Present

Courses

- React.js + Redux
- PHP
- UI/UX
- MySQL for SQL
- Node.js

- Javascript
- Wordpress
- rest API + ajax
- MongoDB
- Firebase + Angular

Jerusalem

Israel

Front-End Developer Nanodegree

Google/Udacity

11/2017 - 08/2018

Front End Development Program, Computer Software freeCodeCamp

09/2017 - 02/2018

WORK EXPERIENCE

Armed Security Officer

Tekoa Security

06/2016 - 05/2017

00/2010-03/2017

Tasks

Maintained constant state of overall security in a gated community

Firewood processor and distributor

Tekoa Firewood

04/2015 - Present

Tasks

- Splitting, handling and bundling firewood, operating equipment
- Operating as part of a team
- moving/sorting, loading and unloading firewood for delivery

MILITARY SERVICE

IDF (03/2012 - 03/2015)

Military Police Detective, Company Educations and Training Logistics NCO, Company Communications and Logistics NCO, Combat Commander

CERTIFICATES

Google/Udacity: Front-End Developer Nanodegree (11/2017 - 08/2018)

freeCodeCamp Certificit of completion - Front End Development Program, Computer Software (09/2017 - 02/2018)

WORK PORTFOLIOS

https://nevehallon.github.io/portfolio_2021

https://nevehallon.github.io/my-app (2018)